The Amanda Seale Show.
The U.S. Supreme Court is considering a homeless ban.
What?
What does that even mean?
A homeless ban?
So we're not going to give you anywhere to live,
but we're going to ban you not having anywhere to live?
Where is this place?
It's questioning if laws against sleeping outside
when no shelter is available are constitutional.
What I believe that they're trying to do
is they're pushing to create sanctuary cities,
which are effectively concentration camps.
You know, like the ghettos that Jewish people
were forced to live in in the Holocaust
while they were awaiting, you know,
being sent to the concentration camps,
like those were still concentration camps.
Even when we talk about Gaza,
Gaza is de facto a concentration camp
because people cannot leave by choice.
So I had Shirley Raines on my show.
Shirley Raines, she works down in Skid Row
here in Los Angeles,
which is the, you know, huge homeless population,
homeless population.
She was like, listen,
when people say I want to be homeless,
it's like the lie that you tell yourself
because you can't figure out
how to get out your situation.
And it really hit me, right?
Because you're like, well, I mean,
that's what people say.
She's like, I'm with them every day.
They don't want to be homeless.
Nobody wants to be homeless.
Yeah.